<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects | Fadhil Ginting</title>
    <link>https://mfadhilgtg.github.io/project/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://mfadhilgtg.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Projects</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 09:20:07 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://mfadhilgtg.github.io/img/icon-192.png</url>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://mfadhilgtg.github.io/project/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>URO ITB</title>
      <link>https://mfadhilgtg.github.io/project/uro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 09:20:07 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mfadhilgtg.github.io/project/uro/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Assessment Center Project</title>
      <link>https://mfadhilgtg.github.io/project/yli_blp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 09:19:47 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mfadhilgtg.github.io/project/yli_blp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The project is part of Young Leaders for Indonesia(YLI) Breakthrough Leadership Program. My team of 5 participants from different background(Geophysical, Civil, Management, and Electrical Engineering Psychology) was assigned to build assessment tools for promotional process in the company. We successfully designed and built the assessment center focusing on the engineering aspects. The project was directly supervised by coaches from McKinsey &amp;amp; Company.
Team: Fadhil Ginting, Marsya Chairuna, Bernadete Ryninta, Nadia Amalia, M. Fajri Taswin.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IoT Workshop</title>
      <link>https://mfadhilgtg.github.io/project/yli_plp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 09:19:43 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mfadhilgtg.github.io/project/yli_plp/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CERN Summer Student Project</title>
      <link>https://mfadhilgtg.github.io/project/cern_gdd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 09:19:04 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mfadhilgtg.github.io/project/cern_gdd/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Like nowhere else on earth! I was delighted to be part of CERN experiments in Geneva. The program offers undergraduate students from across the world to join in the day-to-day work of research teams. The students also have summer student lectures, visits, workshops, poster sessions. In the weekends, you can enjoy beautiful scenery in Switzerland and travel to top destinations in Europe! My project during the internship was to design a program controlled high voltage power supply for micro pattern gaseous detector.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NASA JPL Team CoSTAR for DARPA SubT Challenge</title>
      <link>https://mfadhilgtg.github.io/project/external-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 07:33:13 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mfadhilgtg.github.io/project/external-project/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Terrestrial  underground  robotic  exploration  has  gained  popularity  from  DARPA  Subterranean (SubT) Challenge program. The SubT Challenge require team of robots to rapidly explore, map, navigate  and  search  underground  environments  with  minimal  command  from  a  single  human supervisor.  The  SubT  Challenge  environments  are  ranging  from  mining  tunnels,  abandoned power plant, and natural caves, where robot deployment are important for human safety in various scenarios.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TextVLAD</title>
      <link>https://mfadhilgtg.github.io/project/textvlad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 09:20:33 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mfadhilgtg.github.io/project/textvlad/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multi Camera Deep Tracking and Mapping</title>
      <link>https://mfadhilgtg.github.io/project/deeptam/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 09:20:18 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mfadhilgtg.github.io/project/deeptam/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Visual Odometry methods based on classical 3D geometry have been around for years, using either indirect feature matching or direct visual error minimization. Lately,learning-based methods that combine both matching and geometry estimation in a single network have achieved impressive results. One such method is DeepTAM. Further, it has been shown that classical methods benefit from the extended field of view provided by using multiple cameras. However, these setups have been ignored by current learning-based methods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this work, we extend the existing DeepTAM pipeline to leverage a multi-camera setup with known geometry. We demonstrate the generalizability of DeepTAM to other monocular setups and highlight the scenarios in which it performs poorly. We show the efficacy of our proposed multi-camera VO pipeline to receive better pose estimates using experiments based on simulation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contributors: Mayank Mittal, Rohit Suri, Fadhil Ginting, Parker Ewen&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/surirohit/multi-camera-deeptam&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;https://github.com/surirohit/multi-camera-deeptam&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magic Leap Mixed Reality for Healthcare Application</title>
      <link>https://mfadhilgtg.github.io/project/magicleap/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 07:33:13 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mfadhilgtg.github.io/project/magicleap/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AR-0 Robot Mascot</title>
      <link>https://mfadhilgtg.github.io/project/pk123/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Mar 2018 09:19:31 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mfadhilgtg.github.io/project/pk123/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autonomous Underwater Glider for Marine Exploration</title>
      <link>https://mfadhilgtg.github.io/project/glider/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 07:41:18 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mfadhilgtg.github.io/project/glider/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
